It takes more than a dream to reach the stars.
A Million Miles Away is a drama, history film
directed by Alejandra Márquez Abella.
The life of engineer and former NASA astronaut José M.
Hernández, the first migrant farmworker to go to space.
José Hernández, played by Michael Peña.
Adela, played by Rosa Salazar.
Salvador, played by Julio Cesar Cedillo.
Julia, played by Veronica Falcón.
José (Age 7), played by Juanpi Monterrubio.
Sturckow, played by Garret Dillahunt.
A Million Miles Away is a 2023 American biographical
drama film detailing the life of José M.
Hernández, a Mexican-American astronaut, who is played by Michael Peña.
It was directed by Alejandra Marquez Abella from a screenplay written by Bettina Gilois and re-written
by Hernán Jiménez and Abella, based on Hernandez's autobiography Reaching for the Stars.
The film was released on Amazon Prime Video on September 15, 2023.
The film explores themes of underdog, based on novel or
book, nasa, based on true story, astronaut.
The tone is emotional.